A Must-See Thrill Ride!
From Dusk Till Dawn 3: The Hangman's Daughter is a western,
horror, thriller film directed by P.J. Pesce.
Narrowly escaping death, outlaw Johnny Madrid goes on the run with
the hangman's sensuous daughter Esmeralda by his side.
Johnny Madrid, played by Marco Leonardi.
Ambrose Bierce, played by Michael Parks.
Mary Newlie, played by Rebecca Gayheart.
Esmeralda, played by Ara Celi.
John Newlie, played by Lennie Loftin.
Ezra Traylor, played by Orlando Jones.
From Dusk till Dawn is a 1996 American crime action-horror film directed by Robert Rodriguez
and written by Quentin Tarantino from a concept and story by Robert Kurtzman.
Starring Harvey Keitel, George Clooney, Tarantino, Ernest Liu, and Juliette Lewis, the plot follows a pair of American criminal brothers (Clooney and Tarantino), who take a
family as hostages (Keitel, Liu and Lewis) to cross into Mexico, but ultimately find themselves trapped in a saloon, defending against an even greater threat.
From Dusk till Dawn premiered on January 17, 1996, at the Cinerama Dome theater in
Hollywood, Los Angeles, and was released on January 19 in the United States.
It initially received mixed reviews from critics, who
described the film as well-made if overly violent.
After enjoying financial success at the box office, From Dusk till Dawn has since become a cult film and
spawned a media franchise of sequel films, a video game, and other media adaptations.
The film explores themes of mexico, vampire,
indian territory, outlaw, wild west.
The tone is dark and intense.